btcclicks.com 2019-07-10

# Privacy Policy | BTCClicks

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy and the safety of your information are extremely import to us at BTCClicks. It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we collect from you.

We do not collect any personally identifying information other than what is needed to provide you with our service. We will also let you know why we’re collecting it and how it will be used in the points below.

##### Cookies and Website Analytics

To be able to use our website and its services, cookies need to be enabled. We use cookies to store your preferences and sessions. Without these cookies we will be unable to keep you logged in between sessions. Cookies are also used on our website by our third-party web analytics services. 

Our website uses Google Analytics, which is a service which collects website traffic data to Google's datacenters. Google Analytics does not collect any personally identfying data such as IP addresses or individual user identifiers. Google Analytics is only used to collect aggregated reports about our traffic to better understand how our website is being used. 

##### Data Security

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Whatever data we store, we'll protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 

##### Liability

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we are not liable for the loss or theft of information due to the failure of securing your own device or its compromise. We also link to external websites through links and advertisements that are not operated by us. As we do not have control over their content or practices, we are not responsible or liable for their own privacy policies. 

##### Your Consent

You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of your desired services.

Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel free to contact us.
